{
  "user": {
    "id": "GU2IN73N",
    "name": "Nguyen Van Tu",
    "email": "tunvde170069@fpt.edu.vn"
  },
  "totalQuestions": 10,
  "duration": "15 ph√∫t",
  "startTime": "20:39 - 27/09/2024",
  "endTime": "20:54 - 27/09/2024",
  "answeredQuestions": 7,
  "score": null,
  "questions": [
    { "question": "1 + 1 = ?", "answers": ["1", "2", "3", "4"], "selected": "null", "correct": "2" },
    { "question": "2 + 3 = ?", "answers": ["5", "6", "7", "4"], "selected": "7", "correct": "5" },
    { "question": "5 - 2 = ?", "answers": ["3", "4", "2", "1"], "selected": "4", "correct": "3" },
    { "question": "10 / 2 = ?", "answers": ["5", "6", "4", "3"], "selected": "3", "correct": "5" },
    { "question": "2 x 3 = ?", "answers": ["6", "7", "5", "8"], "selected": "6", "correct": "6" },
    { "question": "4 + 5 = ?", "answers": ["10", "9", "8", "7"], "selected": "9", "correct": "9" },
    { "question": "9 - 4 = ?", "answers": ["6", "5", "7", "4"], "selected": "5", "correct": "5" },
    { "question": "7 + 3 = ?", "answers": ["10", "9", "11", "8"], "selected": "10", "correct": "10" },
    { "question": "6 / 2 = ?", "answers": ["3", "4", "2", "5"], "selected": "3", "correct": "3" },
    { "question": "8 - 3 = ?", "answers": ["5", "6", "4", "3"], "selected": "5", "correct": "5" },
     { "question": "8 - 3 = ?", "answers": ["5", "6", "4", "3"], "selected": "5", "correct": "5" }
  ]
}
